Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - G
        - Grant, Eddy - Eddy Grant (Disc one), 1981; SR-16410; Grant, Eddy (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16411. Double album.
          Catalog # 17.3055/6-F; A-side Matrix # 17.3055-F-A-1N
        - Grant, Eddy - Eddy Grant (Disc two), 1981; SR-16411; Grant, Eddy (Box 283)
          In same jacket as # SR-16410. Double album.
          Catalog # 17.3055/6-G; A-side Matrix # 17.3055-G-A-1N
        - Grant, Eddy - Gimme hope Jo'Anna, 1988; SR-16412; Grant, Eddy (Box 283)
          Catalog # 7 75546-0; A-side Matrix # 7-75546-0-A
          Enigma Records
          Culver City, California
        - Grant, Eddy - Walking on sunshine, 1978; SR-16413; Grant, Eddy (Box 284)
          In same jacket as # SR-16414. Different discs.
          Catalog # 49-03186; A-side Matrix # XSS-170311-1B
        - Grant, Eddy - Walking on sunshine, 1978; SR-16414; Grant, Eddy (Box 284)
          In same jacket as # SR-16413. Different discs.
          Catalog # AS 667; A-side Matrix # XSS-166647-1A
        - Grant, Eddy - Till I can't take love no more (extended version), 1983; SR-16415; Grant, Eddy (Box 284)
          In same jacket as # SR-16416. Multiple copies.
        - Grant, Eddy - Till I can't take love no more (extended version), 1983; SR-16416; Grant, Eddy (Box 284)
          In same jacket as # SR-16415. Multiple copies.
        - Grant, Eddy - Gimme hope Jo'Anna, 1988; SR-16417; Grant, Eddy (Box 284)
          Catalog # K 060-2025146; A-side Matrix # K-060-2025146-A
        - Grant, Eddy - Walking on sunshine; Electric avenue, 2005; SR-16418; Grant, Eddy (Box 284)
          Catalog # AS 667; A-side Matrix # XSS-166647-A
        - Grant, Eddy - Time to let go; California style, 1981; SR-16419; Grant, Eddy (Box 284)
          Catalog # ICET-52; A-side Matrix # ICET 52 A-1U
        - Grant, General - Lootala (kisskidee carnival 1996 road march), 1996; SR-16420; Grant, General (Box 284)
          In same jacket as # SR-16421. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # KRNY 005-A
          Kisskidee Records
          Maraval, Trinidad
        - Grant, General - Lootala (kisskidee carnival 1996 road march), 1996; SR-16421; Grant, General (Box 284)
          In same jacket as # SR-16420. Multiple copies.
        - Grant, General - Run come, 1995; SR-16422; Grant, General (Box 284)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # KRNY 001-A
        - Grant, General - Soca veggie, 1994; SR-16423; Grant, General; Grant, Curtis (Box 284)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # JW-KR-083-A
        - Grant, General - Soca billboard, 1997; SR-16424; Grant, General (Box 284)
          Catalog # KR041090; A-side Matrix # KR-041090-A
          Spice Island
          Queens, New York
        - Grant, Rudy - Sings the hits, 1982; SR-16425; Grant, Rudy (Box 284)
          Catalog # 17.3270/2; A-side Matrix # 17.3270A-1N1
        - Gratitude - I wanna rock you, 1985; SR-16426; Gratitude (Box 284)
          Catalog # PI 18; A-side Matrix # PI-18-A
          Cocoa Records
        - Grav - C'mon; Snake bite, 1998; SR-16427; Grav (Box 284)
          Catalog # 10209-1; A-side Matrix # S-33764
          Correct Records
        - Gravediggaz - Dangerous mindz, 1997; SR-16428; Gravediggaz (Box 284)
          Catalog # GVAB-33507-1; A-side Matrix # GVDJ-33507-1A
          Gee Street
        - Gravediggaz - Dangerous mindz, 1997; SR-16429; Gravediggaz (Box 284)
          In same jacket as # SR-16430. Different discs.
        - Wu-Tang Clan - Protect ya neck; Tearz, 1995; SR-16430; Wu-Tang Clan (Box 284)
          In same jacket as # SR-16429. Different discs.
          Catalog # RDAB 64462-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-64462-1-A1
          Loud Records
        - Gravediggaz - The night the Earth cried, 1997; SR-16431; Gravediggaz (Box 284)
          Catalog # 63881-33509-1; A-side Matrix # 63881-33509-1-A
        - Gravediggaz - The night the Earth cried, 1997; SR-16432; Gravediggaz (Box 284)
        - Gravediggaz - The night the Earth cried, 1997; SR-16433; Gravediggaz (Box 284)
        - Gray Bunnies - He hit me (and it felt like a kiss); Cigarette, 1981; SR-16434; Gray Bunnies (Box 284)
          Catalog # CSX 015; A-side Matrix # CS-015-A
          Clone Records
          Akron, Ohio
        - Gray, Diva - Call me I got what you want, 1983; SR-16435; Gray, Diva (Box 284)
          Catalog # UR 33333; A-side Matrix # UR-33333-A
          Urban Rock Records
        - Gray, Macy - Why didn't you call me, 2000; SR-16436; Gray, Macy (Box 284)
          Catalog # EPC 669519 6; A-side Matrix # 6695196000 1A1
        - Gray, Macy - The id, 2001; SR-16437; Gray, Macy (Box 284)
          Catalog # E 85200; A-side Matrix # AL 85200
        - Gray, Macy - Sweet baby; Hey young world part 2, 2001; SR-16438; Gray, Macy; Badu, Erykah (Box 284)
          Catalog # 671882 6; A-side Matrix # 6718826-A
        - Gray, Macy - Shed, 2001; SR-16439; Gray, Macy (Box 284)
          Catalog # 54866 S1; A-side Matrix # XSS 54866 A
          Sony Music Entertainment
        - Gray, Macy - I've committed murder (Gang Starr remix), 1999; SR-16440; Gray, Macy (Box 284)
          Catalog # EAS 46531 S1; A-side Matrix # XSS-46531-A-1B
        - Gray, Macy - I've committed murder (Gang Starr remix), 1999; SR-16441; Gray, Macy (Box 284)
        - Greans - Mic navigators; Actin'; Funky, 2004; SR-16442; Greans (Box 284)
          Catalog # CFM22; A-side Matrix # CFM 22 A
          Cosmic Flux Musiq
        - Great Peso - It's time to rock, 1984; SR-16443; Great Peso; Mr. Nasty (Box 284)
          Catalog # C.C.L. 401; A-side Matrix # CCL-401-A
          C.C.L. Records Inc.
        - Great Peso - It's time to rock, 1984; SR-16444; Great Peso; Mr. Nasty (Box 284)
        - Greater than one - Now is the time, 1988; SR-16445; Greater than one (Box 284)
          In same jacket as # SR-16446. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # KGK2; A-side Matrix # KGK-2-A
          Kunst = Kapital
        - Greater than one - Now is the time, 1988; SR-16446; Greater than one (Box 284)
          In same jacket as # SR-16445. Multiple copies.
        - Green, Al - I'm still in love with you, 1972; SR-16447; Green, Al (Box 284)
          In same jacket as # SR-16448. Multiple copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # XSHL 32074; A-side Matrix # SLH-647 AL
          Hi Records
          West Memphis, Arkansas
        - Green, Al - I'm still in love with you, 1972; SR-16448; Green, Al (Box 284)
          In same jacket as # SR-16447. Multiple copies. Annotated.
        - Green, Al - Your heart's in good hands, 1995; SR-16449; Green, Al (Box 284)
          Catalog # MCA8P 3577; A-side Matrix # MCA-12466-A
        - Green, Al - Al, 1992; SR-16450; Green, Al (Box 284)
          Catalog # AGREELP1; A-side Matrix # A PORKY PRIME CUT
          Beechwood Music
        - Green, Al - Wait here; To sire with love, 1978; SR-16451; Green, Al (Box 284)
          Catalog # HD 78523; A-side Matrix # H146
          West Memphis, Arizona
        - Green, Al - Love and happiness; Take me to the river, 1977; SR-16452; Green, Al (Box 284)
          Catalog # Disco 3006; A-side Matrix # ZH1 2955-12
          London Disco
        - Green, Al - Blockbuster; Coldblooded, 1983; SR-16453; Green, Al; Green, Al "Baby" (Box 284)
          Catalog # PT-103; A-side Matrix # PT-103-A
          Partytime Records
        - Green, Grant - Blue breakbeats, 1998; SR-16454; Green, Grant (Box 284)
          Catalog # 7243 4 94705 1 4; A-side Matrix # 4947051 A-1-1-1
          Blue Note
        - Green Olives - Shake my day, 1990; SR-16455; Green Olives (Box 284)
          Catalog # X-12082; A-side Matrix # SPIRY-X12082A
          X-Energy Records
        - Green, Rima - Def jazz E.P., 2004; SR-16456; Green, Rima (Box 284)
          Catalog # RIMA-0001; A-side Matrix # RIMA-001-A
          Rima Green Records
        - Green, Vivian - Introducing Vivian Green, 2002; SR-16457; Green, Vivian (Box 284)
          Catalog # CAS 59025; A-side Matrix # XSS 59025 A
        - Green, Vivian - Fanatic, 2003; SR-16458; Green, Vivian (Box 284)
          Catalog # CAS 59263; A-side Matrix # XSS 59263 A
        - Green Wheels - Brand new key, 1979; SR-16459; Green Wheels (Box 284)
          Catalog # PRO 7766; A-side Matrix # PRO 7766-AS-1C
          Ariola Records America
          Beverly Hills, California
        - Greenhouse Effect - Paperchaserz, SR-16460; Greenhouse Effect (Box 284)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # AR-38410-A
          Infinite Earwax
          Pombano Beach, Florida
        - Greenman - Birth, 2000; SR-16461; Greenman (Box 284)
          Catalog # Superstition 2116; A-side Matrix # 321716-6
          Superstition
        - Gregory "D" - "D" rules the nation, 1989; SR-16462; Gregory "D"; D.J. Mannie Fresh (Box 284)
          Catalog # X-101; A-side Matrix # X101A
          Yo! Records
          Dallas, Texas
        - Grenique - Should I, 1999; SR-16463; Grenique (Box 284)
          Catalog # U8P-1470; A-side Matrix # U8P-1470A
        - Grenique - Should I, 1999; SR-16464; Grenique (Box 284)
        - Grey & Hanks - Dancin', 1978; SR-16465; Grey & Hanks (Box 284)
          Catalog # JD-11458; A-side Matrix # PD-41458A 1S F1
        - Grey, Lauren - Putting the night on hold; Irresistible love, 1987; SR-16466; Grey, Lauren (Box 284)
          Catalog # DG-50; A-side Matrix # DG-50-A
          Dice Records
        - Grey Parade - Exteriors, 1983; SR-16467; Grey Parade (Box 284)
          Catalog # 12 RIA 18; A-side Matrix # 12-RIA-18-A
          Rialto
        - Grey, Roman - Look me in the eyes, 1982; SR-16468; Grey, Roman (Box 285)
          Catalog # EMC2-1; A-side Matrix # EMC2-1A-Re-1
        - Greyboy - Soul mosaic (Disc one), 2004; SR-16469; Greyboy (Box 285)
          In same jacket as # SR-16470. Double album.
          Catalog # URLP144; A-side Matrix # S-53848
          Ubiquity
          Costa Mesa, California
        - Greyboy - Soul mosaic (Disc two), 2004; SR-16470; Greyboy (Box 285)
          In same jacket as # SR-16469. Double album.
          Catalog # URLP144; A-side Matrix # S-53850
        - Grieg, Edvard - Peer Gynt suites no. 1 and no. 2; Lyric suite, 1962; SR-13793; Grieg, Edvard; Prague Symphony Orchestra; Neuman, Vaclav (Box 285)
          Catalog # PLPS-160; A-side Matrix # PLPS-160A
          Parliament
        - Griff, KW -, 2003; SR-16471; Griff, KW; DJ Patrick; Mr. Motts (Box 285)
          Catalog # QR-043; A-side Matrix # QR 043 A
          Quiet Records
        - Griff, KW - Dis funkyjoint!, 1998; SR-16472; Griff, KW (Box 285)
          Catalog # FB-106; A-side Matrix # FB-106-A
          Fully Blown Records
        - Griff, KW - Time of my life, SR-16473; Griff, KW (Box 285)
          Catalog # QR-042; A-side Matrix # QR 042 A
        - Griffin - Hot fingers, 1984; SR-16474; Griffin (Box 285)
          Catalog # 1-25123; A-side Matrix # 1-2-5123-A-SH-2
        - Griffin, Billy - Serious, 1983; SR-16475; Griffin, Billy (Box 285)
          Catalog # AS 1807; A-side Matrix # XSS-169553-1A
        - Griffin, Billy - Hold me tighter in the rain, 1982; SR-16476; Griffin, Billy (Box 285)
          In same jacket as # SR-16477. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # CBS A 13 2935; A-side Matrix # CBS A 13 2935 A1
        - Griffin, Billy - Hold me tighter in the rain, 1982; SR-16477; Griffin, Billy (Box 285)
          In same jacket as # SR-16476. Multiple copies.
        - Griffin, Billy - Respect, 1983; SR-16478; Griffin, Billy (Box 285)
          Catalog # AS 1737; A-side Matrix # XSS-169440-1A
        - Griffin, Billy - Respect, 1983; SR-16479; Griffin, Billy (Box 285)
          Catalog # FC 38924; A-side Matrix # AL-38924-2B
        - Griffin, Mary - Knock on wood (euro mixes), 1998; SR-16480; Griffin, Mary (Box 285)
          Catalog # PR 8829; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-89216-89026-1
          Curb Records
          Manchester, United Kingdom
        - Griffith, Roni - (The best part of) breakin' up, 1982; SR-16481; Griffith, Roni (Box 285)
          Catalog # SPV 54; A-side Matrix # SPV-54A-1A
          Vanguard
        - Griffith, Roni - Love is the drug; That's rock and roll, 1982; SR-16482; Griffith, Roni (Box 285)
          Catalog # SPV 56; A-side Matrix # SPV-56T-1A
        - Grind Family - Happy; Groupie, 2000; SR-16483; Grind Family (Box 285)
          Catalog # NGNG-001; A-side Matrix # NGNG-001-A
          No Guts No Glory Records
        - Grind Family - Happy; Groupie, 2000; SR-16484; Grind Family (Box 285)
        - Grizzly Cat - Water bed; Long time god, 1998; SR-16485; Grizzly Cat (Box 285)
          Catalog # 253-05; A-side Matrix # 9-25305-A
          Life Records
        - Grizzly Cat - Water bed; Long time god, 1998; SR-16486; Grizzly Cat (Box 285)
        - Grodeck Whipperjenny - The Grodeck Whipperjenny, 1970; SR-16487; Grodeck Whipperjenny (Box 285)
          In same jacket as # SR-16488. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # PS-3000; A-side Matrix # 3972-PS 3000-1
          People
        - Grodeck Whipperjenny - The Grodeck Whipperjenny, 1970; SR-16488; Grodeck Whipperjenny (Box 285)
          In same jacket as # SR-16487. Multiple copies.
        - Groove Armada - If everybody looked the same, 2000; SR-16489; Groove Armada (Box 285)
          Catalog # JDAB-42710-1; A-side Matrix # 01241-42710-1A
          Jive Electro
        - Groove Armada - My friend (Disc one), 2001; SR-16490; Groove Armada (Box 285)
          In same jacket as # SR-16491. Double album.
          Catalog # JDCD-42988-1; A-side Matrix # JDCD-42988-1A
        - Groove Armada - My friend (Disc two), 2001; SR-16491; Groove Armada (Box 285)
          In same jacket as # SR-16490. Double album.
          Catalog # JDCD-42988-1; A-side Matrix # JDCD-42988-1C
        - Groove Armada - Final shakedown, 2002; SR-16492; Groove Armada (Box 285)
          Catalog # 01241-40056-1; A-side Matrix # JDAB-40056-1A
        - Groove Armada - Superstylin', 2001; SR-16493; Groove Armada (Box 285)
          Catalog # JDAB-42898-1; A-side Matrix # JDAB-42898-1A
        - Groove Armada - Goodbye country (hello nightclub) (Disc one), 2001; SR-16494; Groove Armada (Box 285)
          In same jacket as # SR-16495. Triple album.
          Catalog # 6385 9 2221 71 0; A-side Matrix # 9222171-A
          Zomba Records
        - Groove Armada - Goodbye country (hello nightclub) (Disc three), 2001; SR-16495; Groove Armada (Box 285)
          In same jacket as # SR-16494. Triple album.
          Catalog # 6385 9 2221 71 0; A-side Matrix # 9222171-E
        - Groove Armada - I see you baby - the Belgian remixes, 2000; SR-16496; Groove Armada (Box 285)
          Catalog # ZOM 013; A-side Matrix # 20MBA
        - Groove Armada - My friend, 2001; SR-16497; Groove Armada (Box 285)
          Catalog # 9230530; A-side Matrix # 9230530-A1
          Pepper Records
        - Groove Armada - Superstylin', 2001; SR-16498; Groove Armada (Box 285)
          Catalog # JDAB-42977-1; A-side Matrix # JDAB-42977-1A
        - Groove Ascender - Groove on, 1997; SR-16499; Groove Ascender (Box 285)
          Catalog # TREE 011; A-side Matrix # Tree-011-A
          Tree Records
        - Groove Cartel - The tempo tantrum EP, 1995; SR-16500; Groove Cartel (Box 285)
          Catalog # TNT-47; A-side Matrix # TNT-047-A
          TNT Records
        - Groove Collective - Lift off, 1996; SR-16501; Groove Collective (Box 285)
          Catalog # GSR8P-5253; A-side Matrix # GSP-8P-5253-A
          Giant Step Records
        - Groove Collective - Nerd, 1994; SR-16502; Groove Collective (Box 285)
          Catalog # 0-41432; A-side Matrix # 0-41432-A-SR1
        - Groove Collective - Nerd, 1994; SR-16503; Groove Collective (Box 285)
        - Groove Theory - 4 shure, 1997; SR-16504; Groove Theory (Box 285)
          Catalog # 44 79410; A-side Matrix # XSS-79410A-1B
        - Groove Theory - 4 shure, 1997; SR-16505; Groove Theory (Box 285)
        - Groove Theory - Keep tryin', 1995; SR-16506; Groove Theory (Box 285)
          Catalog # EAS 7515; A-side Matrix # XSS-7515-A
        - Groove Theory - Tell me, 1995; SR-16507; Groove Theory (Box 285)
          Catalog # EAS 7152; A-side Matrix # XSS-7152-A2
        - Groove Theory - Am I gonna be the one, 1995; SR-16508; Groove Theory (Box 285)
          Catalog # MIC 607; A-side Matrix # MIC-607ARE1
        - Groovism - Moving me, 1995; SR-16509; Groovism (Box 285)
          Catalog # TRANS 001; A-side Matrix # T001-A
          Transparent Records
        - Group Home - Suspended in time; Tha realness, 1996; SR-16510; Group Home (Box 285)
          Catalog # PR12 321-1; A-side Matrix # PR-12-321-1-A
          Payday
        - Growin Pains - Still same game, 1998; SR-16511; Growin Pains (Box 285)
          Catalog # HBR3002; A-side Matrix # B812063-01 A1 MK
          Home Brew Records
          Sweden
        - Grupo Batuque - Keyzer (Kenny Dope remixes), 2000; SR-16512; Grupo Batuque; Kenny Dope (Box 285)
          Catalog # FARO 043; A-side Matrix # FARO 043 A-1-1-1
          Far Out Recordings
        - Grusin, Dave - Dave Grusin and the N.Y. / LA. Dream Band, 1982; SR-16513; Grusin, Dave; N.Y. / LA. Dream Band (Box 285)
          Catalog # GRP-A-1001; A-side Matrix # GRP A 1001 A
          GRP
        - G.T. - I need you, 1988; SR-16514; G.T. (Box 285)
          Catalog # DMD 1156; A-side Matrix # STDM 54299-54302-1
        - G.T. - I need you, 1988; SR-16515; G.T. (Box 285)
        - G.T. - Down for the count, 1983; SR-16516; G.T. (Box 285)
          Catalog # SP-17253; A-side Matrix # SP017253A-ES1
        - GTA - The parti EP, 1998; SR-16517; GTA; Simply Jeff (Box 285)
          In same jacket as # SR-16518. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # OT 007; A-side Matrix # OT-007-A1
          Orbit Transmission Records
          Orange County, California
        - GTA - The parti EP, 1998; SR-16518; GTA; Simply Jeff (Box 285)
          In same jacket as # SR-16517. Multiple copies.
        - Guantanamera - Tomorrow is another day; Walking on a cloud, 1988; SR-16519; Guantanamera (Box 285)
          Catalog # Uranus 623; A-side Matrix # 623A-PR1
          Uranus Records
        - Guardian - Sinister Lady, 1982; SR-16520; Guardian (Box 286)
          Catalog # CY-901; A-side Matrix # CY-901-A
          Cyclops Records
        - Gucci Boys - Blockhead, 1987; SR-16521; Gucci Boys (Box 286)
          Catalog # JPI-2009; A-side Matrix # JPI-2009-A
          Jam Packed
        - Gucci Crew II - N.T.S., 1989; SR-16522; Gucci Crew II (Box 286)
          Catalog # HAL 13; A-side Matrix # HAL-13P-A
          Gucci Records
        - Gucci Man - Just the other day; Just don't wanna be lonely, 1990; SR-16523; Gucci Man (Box 286)
          Catalog # SOFT-89-202; A-side Matrix # SOFT-89-202-A
          State Of Fresh Records
        - Gucci Steve - Ain't no Xmas in the hood, 1993; SR-16524; Gucci Steve (Box 286)
          Catalog # OT-5004; A-side Matrix # OT-5004-A
          O-Town Records
          Orlando, Florida
        - Guem - O universo ritmico de Guem, 1982; SR-16525; Guem (Box 286)
          Catalog # SDG 010/82; A-side Matrix # SDG 010/82 2 01
          Som Da Gente
        - Guem - O universo ritmico de Guem, 1982; SR-16526; Guem (Box 286)
        - Guerilla Black - Say what, 2005; SR-16527; Guerilla Black; Hot Dollar (Box 286)
          Catalog # 7087-6-19171-1-6; A-side Matrix # 7087-6-19171-1-6 A
        - Guerilla Black - You're the one, 2004; SR-16528; Guerilla Black (Box 286)
          Catalog # 7087 6 18835 1 0; A-side Matrix # 07243-867461-15A
        - Guerreiro, Cid - Corre corre, 1995; SR-16529; Guerreiro, Cid (Box 286)
          Catalog # 443.071; A-side Matrix # 443071 A
          Amostra Invendável
          Rio de Janeiro, Brazil
        - Guerreiro, Cid - Sina, 1995; SR-16530; Guerreiro, Cid (Box 286)
          Catalog # 443.072; A-side Matrix # 443072 A
        - Guerreiro, Cid - Sina, 1995; SR-16531; Guerreiro, Cid (Box 286)
        - Guerreiro, Cid - Reggae do morro, 1995; SR-16532; Guerreiro, Cid (Box 286)
          Catalog # 443.069; A-side Matrix # 443069 A
        - Guerreiro, Cid - Funk in Bahia, 1995; SR-16533; Guerreiro, Cid (Box 286)
          Catalog # 443.068; A-side Matrix # 443068 A
        - Guess - It's you that I need; Tell me where it hurts, 1993; SR-16534; Guess (Box 286)
          Catalog # 0-41603; A-side Matrix # 0-41603A-SR1
        - Guess Who - Reunion (Disc one), 1984; SR-16535; Guess Who (Box 286)
          In same jacket as # SR-16536. Double album.
          Catalog # PJ 4205; A-side Matrix # PJ 4205 A1
          The Hennel Corporation Inc.
        - Guess Who - Reunion (Disc two), 1984; SR-16536; Guess Who (Box 286)
          In same jacket as # SR-16535. Double album.
          Catalog # PJ 4205; A-side Matrix # PJ 4205 C1
        - Guibert, Bod - Bod Guibert, SR-16537; Guibert, Bod (Box 286)
          Catalog # DM 29; A-side Matrix # DM 1 2/9 A1
          DEG Music
        - Guru - What the f..k; Pure dynamite, 2002; SR-16538; Guru; Noe Money (Box 286)
          Catalog # BBM 004; A-side Matrix # BBM-004-A
        - Gus Gus - Dance you down; Your moves are mine, 2002; SR-16539; Gus Gus (Box 286)
          Catalog # MM 88484-1; A-side Matrix # MM 88484-1A
          Moonshine Music
        - Gus Gus - Desire (Disc one), 2002; SR-16540; Gus Gus (Box 286)
          Catalog # MM 88486-1; A-side Matrix # MM-88486-1-A
        - Gus Gus - Desire (Disc two), 2002; SR-16541; Gus Gus (Box 286)
          Catalog # MM 88486-1; A-side Matrix # MM-88487-1-A
        - Gusto - Disco's revenge, 1995; SR-16542; Gusto (Box 286)
          Catalog # BBR 016-1; A-side Matrix # BBR-016-A
          Bumble Beats Records
        - Gusto - Materialistic girl, 1987; SR-16543; Gusto (Box 286)
          Catalog # PRO-450; A-side Matrix # PRO-450-A
        - Gusto - Materialistic girl, 1987; SR-16544; Gusto (Box 286)
        - Gusto - Disco's revenge, 1995; SR-16545; Gusto (Box 286)
          Catalog # BBR 014-1; A-side Matrix # REVENGE 014-1-A
        - Gusto - Disco's revenge, 1995; SR-16546; Gusto (Box 286)
          Catalog # BBR 014-1; A-side Matrix # BBR-014-1A
        - Guthrie, Gwen - Ain't nothin' goin' on but the rent, 1986; SR-16547; Guthrie, Gwen (Box 286)
          Catalog # 885 106-1; A-side Matrix # 885-106-1-AS-DJ-ES
        - Guthrie, Gwen - Outside in the rain, 1986; SR-16548; Guthrie, Gwen (Box 286)
          Catalog # 885 362-1 DJ; A-side Matrix # 885 362-1C-1
        - Guthrie, Gwen - Ticket to ride, 1987; SR-16549; Guthrie, Gwen (Box 286)
          Catalog # PRO 444; A-side Matrix # PRO-444 A
        - Guthrie, Gwen - (They long to be) close to you, 1986; SR-16550; Guthrie, Gwen (Box 286)
          Catalog # 885 528-1; A-side Matrix # 885-528-1-AS-HRM
        - Guthrie, Gwen - Can't love you tonight, 1988; SR-16551; Guthrie, Gwen (Box 286)
          In same jacket as # SR-16552. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # 0-20859; A-side Matrix # 0-20859-A-SH1
        - Guthrie, Gwen - Can't love you tonight, 1988; SR-16552; Guthrie, Gwen (Box 286)
          In same jacket as # SR-16551. Multiple copies.
        - Guy - Spend the night (extended version), 1989; SR-16553; Guy (Box 286)
          Catalog # MCA-23958; A-side Matrix # MCA-8986 FDS-1
        - Guy - Guy, 1988; SR-16554; Guy (Box 286)
          Catalog # MCA-42176; A-side Matrix # MCA-7794-FW2
        - Guy - Dancin', 1999; SR-16555; Guy (Box 286)
          Catalog # MCA8P-4426; A-side Matrix # MCA 13579
        - Guy - Let's stay together, 1992; SR-16556; Guy (Box 286)
          Catalog # MCA12-54288; A-side Matrix # MCA 11156 FDS-1
        - Guy - Round and round (merry go 'round of love) (12'' extended version), 1988; SR-16557; Guy (Box 286)
          Catalog # MCA-23898; A-side Matrix # MCA-8233-FW1
        - Guy - The future, 1990; SR-16558; Guy (Box 286)